Guide to the Lolo National Forest Collection 1894-1987
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Work diaries, 1946-1957; Series II; 2.5 linear feet
  - Ross P. Middlemist, April 7, 1957-May 5, 1957 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, May 5, 1957-June 2, 1957 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Ross P. Middlemist, June 2, 1957-June 30, 1957 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - William L. Poulson, January 1, 1956-January 31, 1956 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - William L. Poulson, February 1, 1956-February 29, 1956 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - William L. Poulson, March 1, 1956-April 10, 1956 (Box-folder 11/28)
  - William L. Poulson, April 11, 1956-May 14, 1956 (Box-folder 11/29)
  - William L. Poulson, May 14, 1956-June 15, 1956 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - William L. Poulson, June 16, 1956-July 15, 1956 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - William L. Poulson, July 16, 1956-August 9, 1956 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - William L. Poulson, August 10, 1956-September 9, 1956 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - William L. Poulson, September 10, 1956-October 12, 1956 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - William L. Poulson, October 13, 1956-November 19, 1956 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - William L. Poulson, November 20, 1956-December 27, 1956 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - William L. Poulson, December 28, 1956-February 1, 1957 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - William L. Poulson, February 2, 1957-March 9, 1957 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - William L. Poulson, March 10, 1957-April 14, 1957 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - William L. Poulson, April 15, 1957-May 19, 1957 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - William L. Poulson, May 20, 1957-June 20, 1957 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - William L. Poulson, June 21, 1957-July 26, 1957 (Box-folder 12/11)
- Reports, 1935-1937; Series III; 0.4 linear feet
  This series contains Lolo National Forest copies of reports on game and campground improvements.
  - Campground Improvement Guide - Region One, 1935 (Box-folder 12/12)
    Copy contains notes by E.H. Myrick
  - Campground Improvement Guide - Region One, 1935 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Cabinet National Forest: Winter Game Study, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 12/14)
    Cover on title is First Report of the Cabinet Winter Big Game Study Covering the Winter of 1934-1935. Written by G.H. Duvendack.
  - Cabinet National Forest: Winter Game Study, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 12/15)
    Written by Alban Roemer
  - Cabinet National Forest: Winter Game Study, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Fish Creek: Winter Game Study, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Lolo National Forest: Game Studies Report, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 13/1-2)
- Publications, 1924-1982; Series IV; 0.3 linear feet
  This series contains files related to Thirty-Two Years in the Mule Business, which is about the Ninemile Remount Station in Lolo National Forest and was published by the United States Forest Service. The USFS contracted Jane Benson to write the publication and the files are likely Benson’s files for the book. The drafts and correspondence related to the creation of the book have been placed in front of the research files created by Benson.
  - Draft of Thirty-Two Years in the Mule Business, circa 1978 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1982 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Administrative file on improvements to Ninemile Remount Station, 1935-1942 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Articles and manuals, 1943-1969 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Newsletters, 1934-1977 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Notes from oral histories, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Records pertaining to animals kept at Ninemile Remount Station, 1924-1961 (Box-folder 13/9)
- Maps, 1931-1973; Series V; 1.6 linear feet
  This series contains dozens of maps and reports of local terrain and resources centering around peaks and lookouts within the forest. These maps are arranged according to numbers assigned to them by the records creator. Most maps are also titled according to the peak or lookout from which the map was created.
  - 9 Paradise Peak, 1932 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - 10 Kennedy Mountain, 1932 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - 11 Patrick's Knob, 1932-1936 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - 13 and 14 Camel's Hump, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - 24 Eustache Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - 25 Cascade Mountain, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - 26 Keystone Lookout, 1932-1938 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - 32 3-point Mountain, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - 33A Up Up Mountain, 1932-1938 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - 35 Penrose Peak, 1931-1938 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - 41 Little Joe Lookout, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - 47 Mount Bushnell, 1932-1934 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - 50 Jo Jo Mountain, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - 51 Dog Face Mountain, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - 74 Robin Run Moutnain, undated (Box-folder 14/15)
  - 100 Clear Peak, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - 101 Leo Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - 101 and 101A White Mountain, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - 103 Montana Creek Ridge, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - 103 Helwick Peak, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - 105 Flat Iron Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - 106 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - 106 Salt Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - 107 Baldy Point, 1933 (Box-folder 14/24)
  - 109 Driveway Peak, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 14/25)
  - 110 Lolo Springs, 1936 (Box-folder 14/26)
  - 110 Andy's Knob, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/27)
  - 111 Cooper Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/28)
  - 112 Vet's Point, 1933 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - 113 Table Top, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 14/30)
  - 114 Hill Seven, 1933 (Box-folder 14/31)
  - 114 Lolo, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/32)
  - 115 Clark's Peak, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 14/33)
  - 116 Homestead Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/34)
  - 116 Lolo - White Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 14/35)
  - 117 Eddy Peak, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 14/36)
  - 117 Lolo - West Fork Butte, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 14/37)
  - 118 Snider Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 14/38)
  - 119 Sleepy Point, 1933 (Box-folder 14/39)
  - 120 Priscilla Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/40)
  - 121 and 122 Mount Silcox, 1936 (Box-folder 14/41)
  - 123 Honeymoon Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/42)
  - 124 Cube Iron, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/43)
  - 125 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 14/44)
  - 126 Mount Headley, 1933 (Box-folder 14/45)
  - 130 Huckleberry Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/46)
  - 138 Mormon Peak, 1933-1968 (Box-folder 14/47)
  - 164 Graves Peak, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 14/48)
  - 165 Liver Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 14/49)
  - 166 Marmont Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/50)
  - 168 Clear Creek, undated (Box-folder 14/51)
  - 170 Mount of Nancy Creek, 1936 (Box-folder 14/52)
  - 171 Cabin Creek, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 14/53)
  - 173 Copper Gulch, 1936 (Box-folder 14/54)
  - 201 Burnt Fork Pinnacle, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 14/55)
  - 204 and 204A Blue Ridge, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 14/56)
  - 220 Edith Peak, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 14/57)
  - 223 Charity Lookout, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 14/58)
  - 224 Cayuse Hill, 1933-1956 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - 225 Martina Point, 1934 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - 226 Ellis Point, 1934 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - 227 Papoose Point, 1934-1938 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - 238 Petty Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - 301 Stark Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - 302 untitled, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - 303 Brinser Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - 304 Cobden Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - 306 Alice Creek, 1933 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - 307 Stark Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - 308 Verde Creek Point, 1933 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - 309 Sunrise Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - 310 Lake Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - 311 Graham Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - 312 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - 313 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - 314 Freezeout Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - 315 Freezeout Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - 316 Martel Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - 317 Quartz Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - 318 Triangle Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - 319 untitled, 1933-1959 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - 325 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - 326 untitled, undated (Box-folder 15/25)
  - 327 Plateau Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/26)
  - 328 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 15/27)
  - 329 Deer Peak, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - 331 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 15/29)
  - 333 Hill 343, 1933 (Box-folder 15/30)
  - 333 Hill 343, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/31)
  - 336 Cedar Peak, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 15/32)
  - 339 Schley Mountain, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 15/33)
  - 401 Cherry Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/34)
  - 402 Millers Hill, 1933 (Box-folder 15/35)
  - 403 Sacajewea Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/36)
  - 404 Arvilla Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/37)
  - 405 Eagle Tail Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 15/38)
  - 406 Combpest Point, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/39)
  - 407 Henry Peak, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 15/40)
  - 408 Snowball Hill, 1933 (Box-folder 15/41)
  - 409 Sears Point, 1931-1933 (Box-folder 15/42)
  - 410 Big Hole Peak, 1931-1936 (Box-folder 15/43)
  - 411 Eagle Nest Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/44)
  - 412 Coney Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/45)
  - 413 Cabin Point, 1933 (Box-folder 15/46)
  - 414 Angus Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/47)
  - 415 Little Thompson Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/48)
  - 416 Cook Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/49)
  - 418 Broken Nose Knob, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/50)
  - 419 Bar Z Peak, 1931-1938 (Box-folder 15/51)
  - 420 Brushy Peak, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 15/52)
  - 420A Schroeder Point, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 15/53)
  - 424 Skookum Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 15/54)
  - 424A Castle Rock, 1935-1939 (Box-folder 15/55)
  - 425 Ruby Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 15/56)
  - 425A Marble Point, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 15/57)
  - 426 Shorthorn Point, 1933 (Box-folder 15/58)
  - 426 Murphy Ridge, 1933 (Box-folder 15/59)
  - 427 Benson Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - 428 Jungle Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - 429 Wade Peak, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - 429 Basin Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - 430 Razorback Ridge, 1933 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - 430 Deerhorn Mountain, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - 431 Mink Peak, 1933-1935 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - 431 Big Spring Point, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - 432 Meditation Knob, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - 432 Cow Camp Peak, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - 433 Thompson Creek, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - 433 Bark Table Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - 433A Robb's Point, 1933 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - 434 Rabbit Creek, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - 434 Rain-in-the-face Mountain, 1933 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - 435 Amador Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - 435 Crows Nest Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - 435A Buffalo Bill Divide, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - 436 Van Ess Point, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - 436 Mudd Point, 1933 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - 437 Van Ess Point, 1933 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - 438 Bear Gulch, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - 439 Landowner Mountain, 1933-1959 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - 439 Border Peak, 1931-1938 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - 440 Murr Peak, 1927-1939 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - 441 Prospector Mountain #2, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - 442 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - 442 Teepee Mountain, 1931 (Box-folder 16/28)
  - 444 Snowstorm Mountain, 1931-1936 (Box-folder 16/29)
  - 445 Graves Peak, 1933 (Box-folder 16/30)
  - 445 Thompson Peak, 1931-1938 (Box-folder 16/31)
  - 446 Welch Gulch, 1933 (Box-folder 16/32)
  - 447 untitled, 1933 (Box-folder 16/33)
  - 447 Lonetree Peak, 1931-1936 (Box-folder 16/34)
  - 449 Bower's Point, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/35)
  - 450 Danny's Point, 1933 (Box-folder 16/36)
  - 451 Hoodoo Point, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/37)
  - 451 Bend Administrative Site, 1933 (Box-folder 16/38)
  - 452 Richards Peak, 1933-1938 (Box-folder 16/39)
  - 452 Pardee Point, 1934 (Box-folder 16/40)
  - 453 Ashmore Point, 1934 (Box-folder 16/41)
  - 454 Freezeout Point, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 16/42)
  - 457 Lost Peak, undated (Box-folder 16/43)
  - 460 Superior Point, 1935 (Box-folder 16/44)
  - 462 Bold Peak, 1933-1936 (Box-folder 16/45)
  - 465 Fishtrap Bend, 1933 (Box-folder 16/46)
  - 467 5 Mile Peak, 1936 (Box-folder 16/47)
  - 467 Poacher Gulch, undated (Box-folder 16/48)
  - 468 Eagle Rock, 1936 (Box-folder 16/49)
  - 468 Murr Bend, undated (Box-folder 16/50)
  - 469 untitled, 1936 (Box-folder 16/51)
  - 469 Clear Creek, 1934 (Box-folder 16/52)
  - 471 Cherry Creek, undated (Box-folder 16/53)
  - 473 Quinn's Lookout, 1931-1934 (Box-folder 16/54)
  - 477 untitled, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 16/55)
  - 500 Monture Ranger Station, 194 (Box-folder 16/56)
  - 501 Fenn Mountain, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/57)
  - 502 Lake Mountain Lookout, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/58)
  - 505 Morrell Mountain Lookout, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/59)
  - 506 Shant Point, 1934 (Box-folder 16/60)
  - 507 Omar Mountain, 1934 (Box-folder 16/61)
  - 508 Center Ridge Lookout, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/62)
  - 509 East Spread Mountain, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 16/63)
  - 510 Evans Peak, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - 512 Cottonwood Point, 1934-1936
  - 513 Spread Mountain, 1934-1963
  - 514 untitled, 1934
  - 515 Ovando Mountain, 1934
  - 516 McCabe Peak, 1934 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - 517 Meridian Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 518 Madison Lookout, 1934
  - 519 Yellow Jacket Point, 1934
  - 521 Falls Point, 1934
  - 522 Dunham Point, 1934
  - 525 Center Ridge, 1936 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - 526 Cottonwood Point, 1936
  - 527 Conger Point, 1936
  - 528-529 untitled, 1936
  - 530 Morrell Patrol, 1934
  - 531 Monahan Mountain, 1936
  - 532 untitled, 1936 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - 534 Conger Point, 1936
  - 535 untitled, undated
  - 537 Foolhen Patrol, undated
  - 538 Foolhen Lookout, undated
  - 540-541 untitled, 1938
  - 550 Monture Hill, 1936 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - 601 Blue Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 602 Mount Jumbo, 1934
  - 603 Miller Peak, 1934-1936
  - 604 Sheep Mountain, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - 605 Gold Creek Peak, 1934-1936
  - 606 Boulder Point, 1934-1936
  - 607 Belmont Point, 1934-1936
  - 608 Mosquito Peak, 1934-1936
  - 609 Mount Stuart, 1934 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - 610 Blanchard Point, 1934
  - 611 Gold Ridge Point East, 1934
  - 612 Blk. Point, 1934
  - 613 Allen Point, 1934
  - 614 Crystal Point, 1934 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - 615 Franklin Point, 1934-1938
  - 616 Triangle Point, 1934-1937
  - 617 Sunflower Mountain, 1934
  - 618 Pattee Mountain, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - 622 Bonner Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 623 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 625 Davis Creek Lookout, 1934-1936
  - 635 O'Keefe Point, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - 636, 640-641 untitled, 1933-1939
  - 642-643 untitled, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - 644 McLeod Peak, 1937
  - 645-646 untitled, 1937
  - 650 Mitten Mountain, 1937
  - 651-652 untitled, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - 653 Davis Point, 1936-1937
  - 654-657 untitled, 1936-1937
  - 658 Miller Peak, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - 659-660 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 700 Seeley Lake Remount Station, 1934-1936
  - 702 Fawn Peak, 1934-1936
  - 704 Richmond Peak Lookout, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - 706 West Fork Point, 1934-1936
  - 707 Marshall Peak, 1934-1936
  - 708 Richmond Patrol, 1934-1936
  - 713 Wrong Peak, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - 714 Placid Peak, 1934-1936
  - 715 Sunset Patrol, 1934-1936
  - 716 Sunset Lookout, 1934-1936
  - 717 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 720 Boles Point, 1934-1936
  - 721 Boles Point, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - 722 Richmond, 1934-1936
  - 723-724 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 800 Bonita Remount Station, 1934-1936
  - 802 Quigg Peak, 1934-1936
  - 803 Iris Point Lookout, 1934-1957 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - 804 Welcome Point, 1934-1957
  - 805 Eagle Point, 1934-1957
  - 806 Harvey Peak, 1934-1957
  - 806A Black Pine, 1934-1957
  - 807 Hogback Point, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - 808 Spink Point, 1934-1936
  - 809 Cleveland Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 810 Burnt Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 811 Green Mountain, 1934-1936
  - 812 Golden Peak, 1934-1936
  - 813 Tyler Peak, 1934 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - 814 Park Mountain, 1934
  - 815 Grizzly Point, 1934
  - 816 Sandstone Point, 1934
  - 817 Elk Point, 1934
  - 819 Moe Point, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 17/20)
  - 820 East Quigg Peak, 1934-1936
  - 821 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 822 Cinnamon Bear Point, 1934-1936
  - 823 untitled, 1934-1936
  - 824 Fisher Point, 1936 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - 830 Solomon Mountain, 1936
  - 852-853 Quigg Peak, 1936
  - 854 Near Cinnamon Bear, 1936
  - 855 untitled, 1936
  - 856-866 untitled, 1936 (Box-folder 17/22)
  - 867-871 untitled, 1936 (Box-folder 17/23)
  - 875 Bateman Point, 1936
  - 876 Moose Mound, 1936
  - 900 Maple Lake Lookout, 1938 (Box-folder 17/24)
  - 901 White Sand, 1938
  - 902-904 Wendover Ridge, 1938
  - 905-906 Round Top, 1938
  - 907-909 Beaver Ridge, 1938
  - 910-913 Jerry Johnson, 1938 (Box-folder 17/25)
  - 914-916 Indian Post Office, 1938
  - 917 Cayuse Junction, 1938
  - 918 untitled, 1938
  - 919 Engineering Crime, 1938
  - 920 untitled, 1938
  - 921 Round Top, 1938 (Box-folder 17/26)
  - 922 untitled, 1938
  - 923 Granite Peak, 1938
  - 924 Battle Ridge, 1938
  - 950 Hungry Rock, 1938
  - Miscellaneous contours and maps based on Boise meridian, 1935-1959 (Box-folder 17/27)
  - Patrol study forms, undated (Box-folder 17/28)
  - Demi-shaped overlay, Deer Lodge Forest, undated (Box-folder 17/29)
  - Fire occurrence data, 1940-73, Missoula District, 1940-1973 (Box-folder 17/30)
- Photographic Materials, 1894-1987; Series VI; 351 images
  This series contains prints and negatives of the Ninemile Remount Station, the mules and horses that were housed there, Civilian Conservation Corps activies in the 1930s and 1940s, fire fighting operations, and other historic photographs of the Ninemile area. The images in this series are mixed in format (3" x 5" prints, 4" x 5" negatives, and 35mm negatives).
  - Air photograph of Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0069)
  - Crowd watching a mule packing demonstration during Ninemile Packing Days, August 11, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0070)
  - Crowd watching a mule packing demonstration during Ninemile Packing Days, August 11, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0071)
  - Residence at the Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0072)
  - Unloading remount trucks at a fire, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0073)
  - Entrance to Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Poor quality. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0074)
  - Rear view of mule packing wire, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0075)
  - Mule packing lumber, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0076)
  - Mule packing beds, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0077)
  - Mule packing hay, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0078)
  - Mule packing beds, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0079)
  - Mule packing lumber, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0080)
  - Mule packing lumber, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0081)
  - Mule packing lumber, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0082)
  - Haying at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0083)
  - Haying at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0084)
  - Raking hay in the field with a 'dump rake', circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0085)
  - Two 'dump rakes' working in the hay field, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0086)
  - Bull rake with hay approaching Beaver Slide, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0087)
  - Haying at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0088)
  - Three bull rakes loaded with hay, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0089)
  - Haying at Ninemile Remount Depot with Beaver Slide, circa 1930s; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0090)
  - Ninemile mules being transported in truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0091)
  - A string of pack mules in front of two aircraft, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0092)
  - Mules unloaded with loads in large pile, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0093)
  - Mule packing equipment, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0094)
  - Horses in Ninemile Remount Depot horse barn, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0095)
  - Forest Service pack mule, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0096)
  - Forest Service pack string, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0097)
  - Unloaded Forest Service pack string, circa 1934-1942; Photo by K.D. Swan (Box 19, Photo number 87-0098)
  - Riders and mules in front of the Winter Range Road, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0099)
  - Forest Service Ranger, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0100)
  - Riders on the Winter Range Road, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0101)
  - Two men holding mules without packs, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0102)
  - Two riders with dogs during Winter Range Operation, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0103)
  - Packing shovels at Ninemile Remount Depot, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0104)
  - View of corrals and animals from a distance from Winter Range Road, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0105)
  - C.H. McLeod and Major Kelley at Ninemile Remount Depot, May 7, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0106)
  - Kootenai Forest stallion at Ninemile Remount Depot, May 7, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0107)
  - Stallion, April 28, 1937; Photo by Leschinsky (NB) (Box 19, Photo number 87-0108)
  - Kootenai Forest stallion at Ninemile Remount Depot, May 7, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0109)
  - Spring roundup at Winter Range, May 7, 1939; Photo by Lew Nichols (Box 19, Photo number 87-0110)
  - Ninemile mules in trucks, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0111)
  - Early stock truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0112)
  - Truck with the sign "Ninemile Depot Pack Train", circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0113)
  - Ninemile Depot Pack Train truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0114)
  - Stock truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0115)
  - REO Speedwagon (front view), circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0116)
  - Ninemile Remount Depot pack train truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0117)
  - Open tail gate of stock truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0118)
  - Closed tail gate of stock truck, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0119)
  - Two stock trucks loaded with mules, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0120)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; McCormick of the Bitterroot "The Mule of Objects." Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0121)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Judges look over Erlewine's string. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0122)
  - Pack train at Ninemile, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0123)
  - Packing hay at Ninemile, circa 1934-1942; Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0124)
  - Remount Packers Field Day Contests, October 2-4, 1930; Haskins of the Kaniksu loading bell mare. Photo by Lloyd Noel (Box 19, Photo number 87-0125)